<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="section4_part_question">
        <item>What is Baptism?</item>
        <item>Baptism is not just plain water, but it is the water included in God\'s command and connected to God\'s Word.\n
            Which word of God is that?</item>
        <item>What benefit does Baptism give?</item>
        <item>It works forgiveness of sins, delivers from death and the devil, and gives eternal salvation to all who believe this, as the word and promise of God declare.\n
            Which word and promise of God are these?</item>
        <item>How can water do such great things?</item>
        <item>What does such baptizing with water signify?</item>
        <item>It signifies that the old Adam in us should, by daily contrition and repentance, be drowned and die with all sins and evil desires, and that a New Man, in turn, should daily emerge and arise, to live before forever before God in righteousness and purity.\n
            Where is this written?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="section4_part_answer">
        <item>Baptism is not just plain water, but it is the water included in God\'s command and connected to God\'s Word.</item>
        <item>Our Lord Christ says in the last chapter of Matthew: Go into all the world and teach all nations, baptizing them in the name of the Father, and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.</item>
        <item>It works forgiveness of sins, delivers from death and the devil, and gives eternal salvation to all who believe this, as the word and promise of God declare.</item>
        <item>Our Lord Christ says in the last chapter of Mark: He who believes and is baptized will be saved; but he who does not believe will be condemned.</item>
        <item>Clearly it is not the water that does it, but the word of God that is in and with the water, and the faith that trusts this word of God in the water. For without God\'s word the water is plain water and no Baptism; but with the word of God it is a Baptism— a water of life, rich in grace, and a washing of regeneration in the Holy Spirit, as St. Paul says to Titus in chapter three: "Through the washing of regeneration and renewing of the Holy Spirit, whom He poured out on us abundantly through Jesus Christ, our Savior, so that we might be justified by His grace and become heirs of eternal life according to hope. This is most certainly true.</item>
        <item>It signifies that the old Adam in us should, by daily contrition and repentance, be drowned and die with all sins and evil desires, and that a New Man, in turn, should daily emerge and arise, to live before forever before God in righteousness and purity.</item>
        <item>St. Paul says to the Romans in chapter six: "We were buried with Christ through Baptism into death, in order that, just as Christ was raised from the dead through the glory of the Father, so we too, should walk in a new life.</item>    </string-array>
</resources>