<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="section1_part_question">
        <item>The First Commandment\n You shall have no other gods.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Second Commandment\n You shall not misuse the name of your God.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Third Commandment\n You shall sanctify the day of rest.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Fourth Commandment\n You shall honor your father and your mother.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Fifth Commandment\n You shall not murder.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Sixth Commandment\n You shall not commit adultery.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Seventh Commandment\n You shall not steal.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Eighth Commandment\n You shall not give false testimony against your neighbor.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Ninth Commandment\n You shall not covet your neighbor\'s house.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>The Tenth Commandment\n You shall not covet your neighbor\'s wife, manservant, maidservant, animals, or anything that is his.\n\nWhat does this mean?</item>

        <item>What Does God Say of All These Commandments?:</item>

        <item>He says: "I the Lord, your God, am a jealous God, who visits the sin of the fathers upon their children who hate Me, to the third and fourth generation; but to those who love Me and keep My commandments, I do good for a thousand generations.
            \n\n What does this mean?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="section1_part_answer">
        <item>We should fear, love, and trust in God above all things.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not curse, swear, practice witchcraft, lie, or deceive by His name; but call upon it in every trouble, pray, praise, and give thanks.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not despise preaching and His Word; but hold it sacred, and gladly hear and learn it.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not despise or anger our parents and those in authority over us; but honor them, serve and obey them, love and cherish them.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not hurt or harm our neighbor in his body; but help and support him in every bodily need.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we lead a pure and chaste life in word and deed, and each one love and honor his spouse.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not take our neighbor\'s money or property, nor get them with deceitful products or dealings; but help him to improve and protect his property and livelihood.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not falsely deceive, betray, or slander our neighbor, or give him a bad reputation; but defend him, speak well of him, and put the best construction on everything.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not scheme to get our neighbor\'s inheritance or house, nor get it in a way that outwardly appears lawful, and so on; but aid and assist him to keep it.</item>

        <item>We should fear and love God, that we do not unharness, coerce, or alienate from our neighbor his wife, servants, or animals; but urge them to stay and do their duty.</item>

        <item>He says: "I the Lord, your God, am a jealous God, who visits the sin of the fathers upon their children who hate Me, to the third and fourth generation; but to those who love Me and keep My commandments, I do good for a thousand generations.</item>

        <item>God threatens to punish all who transgress these commandments; therefore, we should fear His wrath and not disobey them. But He promises grace and every blessing to all who keep them; therefore, we should also love and trust in Him, and gladly obey His commandments.</item>

    </string-array>


</resources>
