<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="section6_part_question">
        <item>What is the Sacrament of the Altar?</item>
        <item>It is the true body and blood of our Lord Jesus Christ, under the bread and wine, instituted by Christ Himself, for us Christians to eat and to drink.\n
            Where is this written?</item>
        <item>What is the benefit of such eating and drinking?</item>
        <item>How can bodily eating and drinking do such great things?</item>
        <item>Who, then, receives such Sacrament worthily?</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="section6_part_answer">
        <item>It is the true body and blood of our Lord Jesus Christ, under the bread and wine, instituted by Christ Himself, for us Christians to eat and to drink.</item>

        <item>The holy Evangelists Matthew, Mark, Luke and St. Paul, write: "Our Lord Jesus Christ, on the night in which He was betrayed, took bread, and when He had given thanks, He broke it and gave it to His disciples and said, 'Take, eat; this is My body, which is given for you. This do in remembrance of Me.'\n In the same way also He took the cup after supper, gave thanks and gave it to them, saying, 'Take, and drink of it, all of you. This cup is the New Testament in My blood, which is shed for you for the forgiveness of sins. This do, as often as you drink it, in remembrance of Me.'"</item>

        <item>That is shown us by these words: "Given and shed for you, for the forgiveness of sins," namely, that in the Sacrament, forgiveness of sins, life, and salvation are given us through these words. For where there is forgiveness of sins, there are also life and salvation.</item>

        <item>Clearly it is not the eating and drinking that does it, but the words that are there: "Given, and shed for you, for the forgiveness of sins." These words accompany the bodily eating and drinking as the chief part in the Sacrament, and whoever believes these words has what they say and as they declare, namely, the forgiveness of sins.</item>

        <item>Fasting and bodily preparation is certainly a fine outward discipline, but he is truly worthy and well-prepared who has faith in these words: "Given, and shed for you, for the forgiveness of sins." But whoever does not believe these words or doubts them is unworthy and unprepared. For the words "for you" require nothing but believing hearts.</item>

    </string-array>


</resources>