<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string-array name="section2_part_question">
        <item>The First Article. Of Creation.\n
            I believe in God, the Father Almighty, Maker of heaven and earth.\n
            What does this mean?</item>
        <item>The Second Article. Of Redemption.\n
            And in Jesus Christ, His only Son, our Lord; who was conceived by the Holy Ghost, born of the Virgin Mary; suffered under Pontius Pilate, was crucified, dead, and buried; He descended into hell; the third day He rose again from the dead; He ascended into heaven, and sitteth on the right hand of God the Father Almighty; from thence He shall come to judge the quick and the dead.\n
            What does this mean?
        </item>
        <item>The Third Article. Of Sanctification. \n
            I believe in the Holy Ghost; one holy Christian Church, the communion of saints; the forgiveness of sins; the resurrection of the body; and the life everlasting. Amen.\n
            What does this mean?
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="section2_part_answer">
        <item>I believe that God has made me, along with all created things; that He has given me my body and soul, eyes, ears, and all my members, my reason and all my senses, and still preserves them; He also richly and daily provides me with clothing and shoes, food and drink, house and yard, wife and children, land, animals, and all that I have— with all that I need to sustain this body and life; He shields me from all danger and guards and protects me from all evil; and all this He does out of pure, fatherly, divine goodness and mercy, without any merit or worthiness in me; for all this it is my duty to thank and praise, to serve and obey Him. This is most certainly true.</item>
        <item>I believe that Jesus Christ, true God, begotten of the Father from eternity, and also true man, born of the Virgin Mary, is my Lord, who has redeemed me, a lost and condemned person, purchased and won me from all sins, from death, and from the power of the devil; not with gold or silver, but with His holy, precious blood and with His innocent suffering and death, that I should be His own and live under Him in His kingdom and serve Him in everlasting righteousness, innocence, and blessedness, just as He is risen from death, lives and reigns forever and ever. This is most certainly true.</item>
        <item>I believe that I cannot by my own reason or strength believe in Jesus Christ, my Lord, or come to Him; but the Holy Spirit has called me by the Gospel, enlightened me with His gifts, sanctified and preserved me in the true faith; even as He calls, gathers, enlightens, and sanctifies the whole Christian Church on earth, and preserves it with Jesus Christ in the one true faith; in this Christian Church He daily and richly forgives all sins to me and all believers, and on the Last Day He will raise me and all the dead and give eternal life to me and all believers in Christ. This is most certainly true.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>